Eyad Hisham

I'm a Software Engineer, I worked in many development roles such as developer, business analyst, project manager, product owner and even account manager.

I created many commercial apps in wide variety of platforms/industries/domains.

I have built 6+ commercial mobile apps, 200+ Photoshop scripts and 8+ commercial web systems.

Contact

Address:

Egypt, cairo, nasr city

Phone:

+20 11 000 99039

Email

eyiadhisham@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/ey-ha96

Github:

github.com/xEyad

Portfolio (images)

Online CV

Technical demos

Visual pathfinder

Algorithm visualizer

C++ Chess game (exe)

Dynamic widgets builder

Elapsed circle

Technical tools

- Flutter
- Angular 5+
- JavaScript
- CSS/SCSS
- Typescript
- Dart
- C++ 14
- C++ 11
- AHK
- QT
- React

Languages

English – B2 Arabic - Native

Experience

CrossWorkers – software engineer

05/2022- present

O QPR Helsinki, Finland (web)

Working With QPR SOFTWARE on the new gen of Strategy management software that serves big companies and public sector using React as frontend framework

- Created performance tracking software for government entities using React, Redux, Material
- Implemented a web-based PowerPoint-like feature for creating complex dashboards using React and Highcharts with the ability to export to PDF and PowerPoint.

Fabrica dev – software engineer

01/2019 - 05/2022

• Waterway (web,ios,android)

Worked on Waterway internal web system. designed and implemented it's EOI module. Also, built it's mobile app using flutter. "Waterway" is a major realestate developer in Egypt and the solution manages their internal CRM system.

• Castle developments (web,ios,android)

Worked on Castle developments internal web system, designed and implemented their helpdesk system and built its **mobile app** that manages their internal CRM and units' reservations using **flutter**

JD Holdings (web)

Worked on JD Holdings internal web system. This system is used by all 4 major developers under the parent company JD Holdings.

• RE/MAX Egypt (web)

Designed, developed and deployed RE/MAX Egypt internal CRM system that operates and manage the

leads coming from the <u>CAPTOUR</u> project and distributing it to sub RE/MAX offices/franchises.

• Connect homes (web)

Designed, developed and deployed the internal web system and mobile app, connect homes is one of major brokers in Egypt. currently holding over 300K leads and works with more than 30+ developers.

Eyad Hisham

I'm a Software Engineer, I worked in many development roles such as developer, business analyst, project manager, product owner and even account manager.

I created many commercial apps in wide variety of platforms/industries/domains.

I have built 6+ commercial mobile apps, 200+ Photoshop scripts and 8+ commercial web systems.

Contact

Address:

Egypt, cairo, nasr city

Phone:

+20 11 000 99039

Email:

eyiadhisham@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/ey-ha96

Github:

github.com/xEyad

Portfolio (images)

Online CV

Technical demos

Visual pathfinder

Algorithm visualizer

C++ Chess game (exe)

Dynamic widgets builder

Elapsed circle

Technical tools

- Flutter
- Angular 5+
- JavaScript
- CSS/SCSS
- Typescript
- Dart
- C++ 14
- C++ 11
- AHK
- QT
- React

Languages

English – B2 Arabic - Native

Experience

Psycoders – software engineer

Project based

O Diet academy (web,ios,android)

Worked on Diet academy web dashboard and built its **mobile app.** Diet academy is solution that enables users to reserve video or chat packages with the doctor and maintain patient information.

Bondo (ios,android)

Worked on Bondo web dashboard and Built its mobile app. Bondo is a small scale social media that operates over the map, where user can record a voicenote and add some metadata to it. then it will be shown over the google map and other users can interact with it.

NewGame (web)

Built NewGame e-commerce website. NewGame is boardgames manufacturer and distributor in egypt.

Egyptian Veterinarians syndicate (<u>ios</u>,android)
Built Egyptian vets syndicate mobile app.

• Venu (ios, android, waiter app)

Built Venu dine in mobile app and its two main components. The client facing app and the waiter pos tablet app

Fiverr - Photoshop Automator (freelance) 01/2017 - present

O Photoshop scripts

Successfully created and delivered over 200 photoshop script and automation solutions to 100+ client in more than 16 country

Education

B.Sc. computer science

2013-2017

- Higher technological institute (HTI)
- GPA: 3.0